(Sheldon:)You better throw in that squirt gun.
Hm... Yeah, I don't know.
This squirt gun, it's... it's pretty rare.
(Sheldon:)Oh!
(Leonard:)And this is me doing
the Titanic pose on the boat.
(Sheldon:)Oh!
(Leonard:)And... oh, that's me getting rescued
after I fell in.
(Penny:)Oh.
(Penny:)-Oh. That's the pizza.
-Yep.
(Leonard:)-Here's some money.
-Thank you.
(Leonard:)And I'm gonna hit the head.
(Leonard:)That's what us salty sea dogs say
when we have to go pee-pee.
-I-\{ey.
-Twenty-two, fifty.
Okay, here's 25.
Keep the change.
(Pizza guy:)Seriously? I just walked up,
like, four flights of stairs.
(Penny:)Oh, okay. Well, here's, um...
Thirty-something cents,
(Penny:)and a promise
I won't call your boss
(Penny:)and tell him
you reek of marijuana.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Penny, I see
you've ordered pizza.
(Sheldon:)-I have Chinese food.
-That's nice.